Yeah, congrats Jonathan on coming to
Indianapolis.
Um, did you have other interest from
other teams and if so, what put Indy
over the top?
Uh, I definitely had other options.
Um, but I just me and my agent really
felt that um, we just felt wanted. They
have been pretty
um, persistent with going back and forth
with communications with my agent
throughout the free agency process.
And it was just something that we
decided was the best fit for us just
um, defensively, special team wise, it
just really felt like a good fit to come
in and be able to compete, so.
Joel.
You mentioned coming in to compete. What
what's your um, knowledge of what the
what's your opportunity is here? Um,
coming in to complete compete man and
play safety. That was uh,
um,
pretty much you know, obviously you look
at the roster, you look at who left.
Um, so there were some voids and
obviously what we who knows what'll
happen in the draft, but
um, just coming in man, being a veteran,
just bringing the type of person that I
am, the way that I play man, just um,
really felt that uh, we could be an
asset to Indy, so.
Nathan.
Hey Jonathan. Um, I know you uh, you had
a couple seasons there where you were
getting lots of starting reps. Um, got a
little bit of that in Chicago and had an
a big impact on the special teams as
well. Um, you were kind of talking about
it a little bit there about um, what the
opportunities are like. What what do you
feel like you bring to the the Colts?
Um, what are your your biggest strengths
when you kind of look at your game at
this point in your career?
Um, versatility for sure. Just whatever
you need me to play man, I'm smart. Um,
can play special teams and defense and
in my I can excel at both.
Um, being a leader man, I have a bunch
of years and snaps that I played in the
NFL man, so being able to pass along the
knowledge that I've
uh, learned and gained throughout my
years and
um, just leadership man and like I said,
the places that I've been um,
the organizations that I've been to and
uh, just like I said, passing along the
knowledge man, but
um, first and foremost is my play my
play style on the field man, so really
excited.
James, go ahead.
Jonathan, what was it like to be a part
of a turnaround in Chicago? Um,
obviously um, you all built something
pretty special there last year, so what
can you take from that experience to
help the Colts get to where they want to
go?
Uh, it was amazing man. Just to like I
said, you come in and
um, I'm not going to say we had a a bad
year the first year, but we didn't win
as much as we wanted to.
Um, but coming into the next season we
just all remembered how that year felt
and it was a collective group that we
just all came along and we just all
moved on the same accord man and
um, just like I said, the knowledge that
I've learned, the things I've learned in
the locker room, how to just carry
myself throughout, how to take care of
my body, just bits and pieces that I've
taken from different people along my
journey man and I I really feel like I
can help the team, so
um, we're just excited to be here man.
Chop.
Yeah, Jonathan, welcome to Indy.
Appreciate you. I guess an obvious
question is
with with you and Simone,
is it difficult? Have you guys I mean
there's there's got to be plusses and
minuses to
to to being involved like that with with
she's a star, you're a star. How has all
that worked? How how
>> Um, you just you just support each
other. I'll go ahead. I'm sorry.
>> So how how have how have you made it
work? Um, you just support each other
man. I mean every relationship has uh,
difficulties that you have to work
through, but um, ours is a little bit
more put on the forefront cuz you know,
you are public figures, but
um, man you just support each other man.
I support her to the fullest when she
was competing and she does the same with
me and
um, honestly it makes you play better
when your significant other is as behind
you as that, so
um, she's my biggest supporter and she
also will tell me if I need to do a
little bit better too man, so I I want
her to be like that. I don't want you to
just tell me that I'm doing amazing all
the time and
um, she just keeps me to that standard
man, so it it helps me to be the best
person that I can be. Has she got her
Colts jersey yet?
Oh, she's getting it. Don't worry about
it.
Nice gear. Plenty gear. Thank you.
Just a few more, James. Yeah, along
those lines and I promise uh, I and
others won't pester you about this all
year, but when it comes to Simone and
what she brings to the sports in
general, what is it like to have
somebody who just brings attention to
the sport even more like not just men,
but kids, girls, whatever, they going
probably tune in because they know that
the goat is watching. Um, man it's
amazing just because of the impact that
she does have and
um, it will bring more eyes, you know,
and so that's one thing that we are
pretty excited about and
um, you know, people know that it comes
with it, so um, we excited man. We
looking forward to this year man. We
just super happy to be here in Indy man
for the opportunity.
And then one more. Um, I like to ask
guys this after you get another
contract. This is a hard league, right?
So um, have you had a moment to maybe
just appreciate how far you've come
because it isn't easy to last this long
in the league. Um, I actually haven't
man. See, my wife keep asking me, how do
you feel? How do you feel? And I I don't
know what to answer yet.
Uh, just because you are you getting a
flow where you just moving and grooving.
Um, I'm sure it'll hit me in a couple
days man, just you know, because it is
another
uh, huge milestone man, just being
undrafted from a D2 school man and I'm
going into my ninth season. So
um, this is one of those things man, you
know,
sometimes other people have to tell you
that you need to take a step back and
appreciate because you get so much into
a flow of working and hustling and
bustling and you just trying to move on
to the next thing, you know, so
um, I'll definitely make sure I take
time to reflect on that man just
um, because it has been a pretty crazy
journey for me and um,
resilience has played a large part into
it, but um,
sometimes I just get caught in just
trying to look forward man and keep my
head down and keep working, you know
what I mean? And sometimes you do
um, have to take a step back man, but I
I appreciate that.